gaydemon.com 2004-12-09

# gaydemon - privacy policy

|  |  |   
---  
 Adult Categories  
 Site Categories  
---  
 Adult Shop  
 Video Online  
 Other  
|  |  |   |  | 

Shop at Gaydemon  
  
---  

| 

| 

Click cover for details and reviews!  
  
  |  | 

Watch Online  
  
---  

(89 min, Italy, Lucas Kazan)  
Rent and watch this movie online NOW at gaydemon!  
Content: Anal Sex, Kissing, Oral Sex  
Men: Muscleboys, Hunks, Latino  | 

| 

---|---  
  
Click to watch this movie now!  

Privacy Policy

|   
---|---  
  
What This Privacy Policy Covers 

  * This policy covers how gaydemon.com treats any personal information that gaydemon.com might have collected and received, including information related to your past use of gaydemon services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that gaydemon does not own or control, or to people that gaydemon does not employ or manage. 

Information Collection and Use  
General 

  * Gaydemon collects personal information if you register with gaydemon as a user, when you use gaydemon services, when you visit gaydemon pages or the pages of certain gaydemon partners.
  * Gaydemon automatically receives and records information on our server from your browser, including your IP address and the page you request. This information is anonymous and are is not linked to any personal details we might have stored.
  * Gaydemon uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, conntact you, and conduct research.
  * Gaydemon will not under any circumstances give out any information that might be stored about you such as email address or any other details to anyone!

Quick and Simple

Gaydemon respects your privacy, any information we might have will not be disclosed or given away to anyone else or any 3rd party.  
  
gaydemon.com has it all! This is a gay internet [directory and search engine](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/index.html). with the best [gay porn sites](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/Pornsites/index.html) and [gay sites](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/Pornsites/index.html) on the net. [free gay porn](http://www.gaydemon.com/porn/pictures.htm), [free gay videos](http://www.gaydemon.com/porn/videos.htm), gay porn as it should be - free! gay [paysite reviews](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/Reviews/index.html), reviewed in detail with free previews. we have free images and [picture galleries](http://www.gaydemon.com/porn/pictures.htm). [free gay videos](http://www.gaydemon.com/porn/videos.htm) to view and download. queer [resources](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/Resources/index.html) and [gay porn sites](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/Pornsites/index.html) of every kind! [online shopping](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/Resources/Shopping/index.html) for the [gay man](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/Pornsites/Men___Boys/index.html). gay chat and forum with profiles. this is a queer website for men with a addiction for gay porn! you can find gay porn sites with [gay boys](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/Pornsites/Men___Boys/index.html) or muscle hunks but also male escorts and gay cartoons. gay [erotic stories](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/Pornsites/Erotica/Erotic_Stories/index.html) to read, [gay fetish](http://www.gaydemon.com/Directory/Pornsites/Fetish/index.html) websites of every kind such as bareback or bdsm and also gay bondage sites or dresscode sites with gay man in underwear, leather or rubber. Other gay fetish sites such as foot fetish sites and boot sites or gay fisting and gay bdsm. there are also gay sex sites with bisexual sex or transexual sex!
